<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>swiftui on Einführung in Swift und SwiftUI</title>
    <link>https://gruendau.github.io/einfuehrung-in-swift-und-swiftui/tags/swiftui.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in swiftui on Einführung in Swift und SwiftUI</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>de-DE</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 20:49:19 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gruendau.github.io/einfuehrung-in-swift-und-swiftui/tags/swiftui/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Anwendungen</title>
      <link>https://gruendau.github.io/einfuehrung-in-swift-und-swiftui/links/apps.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 20:49:19 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gruendau.github.io/einfuehrung-in-swift-und-swiftui/links/apps.html</guid>
      <description>Auflistung von Anwendungen &amp;lt;applications&amp;gt; &amp;lt;apps&amp;gt;.
Name Links Anmerkung Apple home youtube github facebook instagram reddit wiki Docker home docs youtube github twitter facebook linkedin reddit wiki email GitHub home docs blog youtube github twitter facebook twitch linkedin tiktoc wiki Kinsta home docs blog youtube github twitter facebook instagram reddit email WordPress-Hosting Netlify home docs blog tutorials cli youtube github twitter facebook linkedin wiki email Swift home docs blog github twitter reddit wiki Twitter home docs youtube github twitter facebook instagram reddit wiki </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Benutzerdefinierter Modifikator</title>
      <link>https://gruendau.github.io/einfuehrung-in-swift-und-swiftui/kits/swiftui/modifiers/custom-modifiers.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 20:49:19 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gruendau.github.io/einfuehrung-in-swift-und-swiftui/kits/swiftui/modifiers/custom-modifiers.html</guid>
      <description>Text &amp;hellip;
Links:
Configuring SwiftUI views von John Sundell, 2020 Slider: https://swdevnotes.com/swift/2021/how-to-customise-the-slider-in-swiftui/
Discover: https://www.swiftbysundell.com/discover/swiftui/
Links: modifier(_:) von Apple ViewModifier von Apple Declaring a custom view von Apple SwiftUI Custom View Modifiers von Keith Harrison, 2021 How to create custom modifiers von Paul Hudson, 2023 Understanding SwiftUI: Modifiers von Rodrigues, 2020 SwiftUI Custom Styling von Javier, 2019 How to make custom view modifiers in SwiftUI von Simple Swift Guide, 2020 How to conditionally apply modifiers in SwiftUI von Matteo Puccinelli, 2020 How to create custom view modifiers in SwiftUI?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swift/SwiftUI Autoren</title>
      <link>https://gruendau.github.io/einfuehrung-in-swift-und-swiftui/links/authors.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 20:49:19 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gruendau.github.io/einfuehrung-in-swift-und-swiftui/links/authors.html</guid>
      <description>Auflistung von Autoren.
Name Autor Links Anmerkung TechWorld with Nana Nana Janashia home youtube github gitlab twitter LinkedIn email </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swift/SwiftUI Links in englischer Sprache</title>
      <link>https://gruendau.github.io/einfuehrung-in-swift-und-swiftui/links/english.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 20:49:19 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gruendau.github.io/einfuehrung-in-swift-und-swiftui/links/english.html</guid>
      <description>Text &amp;hellip;
Name Autor Links Anmerkung Advanced Swift Robert Pieta home github twitter Alexander Grebenyuk home blog github twitter mastodon Alexey Naumov home blog github twitter Andrew Bancroft home github twitter Antoine von der Lee home github twitter twitter stack instagram email AppCoda home blog github twitter facebook instagram Artturi Jalli home github gist email - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - Benoit Pasquier home github twitter Bolt UIX home youtube github twitter facebook instagram medium byby.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swift/SwiftUI Links in deutscher Sprache</title>
      <link>https://gruendau.github.io/einfuehrung-in-swift-und-swiftui/links/german.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 20:49:19 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gruendau.github.io/einfuehrung-in-swift-und-swiftui/links/german.html</guid>
      <description> Name Autor Links Anmerkung Bodo Schönfeld home youtube github twitter instagram email Der Swift Blog home tutorial 2014-2017 Holger Hinzberg home github twitter email LET&amp;rsquo;S DEV home blog twitter facebook instagram email Martin Lexow youtube twitter instagram mastodon reddit email Paul Hudson home Thomas Sillmann home youtube github email https://www.predic8.de/iOS-swift-app-tutorial.htm http://swift.guru/ https://letsdev.de/blog/swift-ui-einfache-schnelle-umsetzung-von-user-interfaces </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vorlesungen der Stanford University zu SwiftUI</title>
      <link>https://gruendau.github.io/einfuehrung-in-swift-und-swiftui/links/stanford.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 20:49:19 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gruendau.github.io/einfuehrung-in-swift-und-swiftui/links/stanford.html</guid>
      <description>Die Vorlesungen (CS193p) werden von Paul Hegarty gehalten und wurden von der Stanford University öffentlich zugänglich gemacht. Diese verlinkten Videos haben ein anspruchsvolles Niveau und sollten dreimal angeschaut werden &amp;hellip; zum Staunen, zum Verstehen und schlußendlich zum Genießen.
Thank you Paul, thank you Stanford!
Stanford CS193p - Swift 3 with UIKit - Spring 2017 Video Dauer 01 Introduction to iOS 10, Xcode 8 and Swift 3 84 min 02 MVC; iOS, Xcode and Swift Demonstration 85 min 03 More Swift and the Foundation Framework 85 min 04 Views 81 min 05 Gestures and Multiple MVCs 81 min 06 Multiple MVCs, View Controller Lifecycle 84 min 07 Error Handling, Extensions, Protocols, Delegation 79 min 08 Multithreading and Text Field 77 min 09 Table View 90 min 10 Core Data 91 min 11 Core Data Demo 76 min 12 Autolayout 51 min 13 Timer and Animation 81 min 14 Dynamic Animation Demo 82 min 15 More Segues 83 min 16 Alerts and Action Sheets 72 min 17 Accessibility 43 min rauf runter</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
